All will be disclosed.
Disclosure Day is a science fiction film directed by Steven Spielberg.
If you found out we weren’t alone, if someone showed you,
proved it to you, would that frighten you?
Disclosure Day is an upcoming American science fiction film co-produced and directed by
Steven Spielberg, from a screenplay by David Koepp based on a story by Spielberg.
The film stars Emily Blunt, Josh O'Connor, Colin
Firth, Eve Hewson, and Colman Domingo.
In April 2024, it was reported that Spielberg's next project would be a UFO film
based on his original idea, with Koepp writing the screenplay.
Within the next few months, Universal Pictures was announced as
distributor and Blunt was cast in the lead role.
Filming took place from February to May 2025.
Disclosure Day is scheduled to be released in the United
States by Universal Pictures on June 12, 2026.
The tone is thought_provoking.